Rayna Harris, PhD

□ 512-657-2964 | ☑ raynaharris@palisadestahoe.com | 🏕 www.raynaharris.com | 🛅 raynamharris | 💆 raynamharris

Professional Summary _____

I am interested in the Senior Strategy Analyst position at Alterra Mountain Company. I have worked at Palisades Tahoe at Alpine Meadows for four years in the Parking and Information Mountain Host Departments. I have a PhD in Cell and Molecular Biology and ten years of experience managing projects, analyzing data, and making data-driven decisions. My first-hand knowledge of Alterra mountains and ability to strategize and solve problems make me an excellent candidate for the Senior Strategy Analyst position.

Education

The University of Texas at AustinPh.D. Cell and Molecular Biology2012 - 2017The University of Texas at AustinAustinB.S. Biochemistry2002 - 2006

Employment_

Palisades Tahoe at Alpine Meadows - Information Mountain Host Lead

Alpine Meadows, CA
Oct 2023 - Current

Blah, Blah, Blah

South Lake Tahoe, CA

Lake Tahoe Community CollegeAdjunct Faculty, Biology Department

Jan 2023 - June 2024

Palisades Tahoe at Alpine Meadows

Alpine Meadows, CA

PARKING SUPERVISOR

Nov 2020 - Jul 2023

University of California, Davis

Davis, CA

POSTDOCTORAL SCHOLAR

May 2018 - Apr 2023

The University of Texas at Austin

Austin, TX Oct 2010 - Sep 2012

Laboratory Manager

Austin, TX

The University of Texas at Austin

Jan 2007 - Dec 2010

TEACHING SPECIALIST

Jan 2007 - Dec 2010

Computer Skills

Excel, HTML, LaTeX, Outlook, PowerPoint, Python, R, Square, TouchBistro, UNIX, Word

Languages Spoken _____

English, Spanish

Honors and Awards

AAAS COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT FELLOWSHIP

RSTUDIO::CONF 2019 DIVERSITY SCHOLARSHIP

OUTSTANDING GRADUATE STUDENT ACADEMIC EMPLOYEE AWARD

UNIVERSITY GRADUATE CONTINUING FELLOWSHIP

2019

2017

ACADEMIC ENRICHMENT FUND AWARD 2014, 15, 16